<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>220411</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/220411-g9.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The assorted humiliations, disasters and rare triumphs of four very different twenty-something girls: Hannah, an aspiring writer; Marnie, an art gallery assistant and cousins Jessa and Shoshanna.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-04-15</FirstAired>
<Network>HBO</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1723816</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP0151858200</zap2it_id>
<id>220411</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>300674</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls Can Code</SeriesName>
<Overview>Talent show with a difference, in which five girls unleash the digital guru within themselves.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-09-14</FirstAired>
<Network>BBC Three</Network>
<id>300674</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>271200</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Travel Girls</SeriesName>
<Overview>Six girls have been chosen to compete for the chance to be a television star with their own travel show. Traveling to Tokyo, Thailand, Sydney, Paris and Rome these girls will have to produce their own travel stories in each location, facing challenges with the locals, the production team and each other! Watch as the girls attempt to overcome their lack of experience as travel hosts while still trying to stay ahead of the other girls and move on in the competition. The five competing Travel Girls all touch down in their first location Bangkok, Thailand. After a production meeting it is time to get into the competition. Working through the day and night the girls are tested at Bangkok’s markets with pieces they have to perform to camera. But is the stress of the competition already too much for some of the girls? Problems are also already starting in the crew, as the executive producer goes head to head with the series producer. </Overview>
<id>271200</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>80221</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Fight Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/80221-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Ten female fighters from the United States convene in Las Vegas for the chance to travel to Thailand to compete against the world’s best in a Muay Thai championship fight. Muay Thai, or Thai Boxing, the national sport of Thailand, is considered by some to be the deadliest form of martial arts. The show captures the life both inside and outside the gym through six grueling weeks of training under the supervision of Master Toddy, culminating in the main event in Thailand. Who will be left standing in the ring?</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-06-12</FirstAired>
<Network>Oxygen</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0893074</IMDB_ID>
<id>80221</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>303147</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls Beyond the Wasteland</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Girls aim for the Wilderness: Girls beyond the youth KOYA|Girls beyond the youth KOYA|Shōjo-tachi wa Kōya o Mezasu|Shoujo-tachi wa Kouya wo Mezasu</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/303147-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Buntarou doesn't know what he wants to do in the future. He does not have any kind of dream that he wants to pursue, so currently he just spends his days hanging around with his friends. One day, his classmate Sayuki asks him if he wants to help with development of a gal game. She says that she had become interested in his help after she read one his works intended for the drama club.

Buntarou doesn't know anything about gal games, but Sayuki claims that she has the ability to make it a success. Can they make the game, and will it be a success like she claims it will be? This is the story of youths taking a daring step into the unknown...</Overview>
<FirstAired>2016-01-07</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo MX</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt5326434</IMDB_ID>
<id>303147</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>244881</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Curl Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/244881-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Curl Girls is a 6-part television reality series that premiered on the Logo Television Network on June 18, 2007. Curl Girls is the first lesbian reality show on a major network. It chronicles the friendships and careers of Gingi, Michele, Melissa, Erin, Vanessa, and Jessica – six young lesbian women. Although the six women have different personalities and careers, all enjoy surfing. During the course of this series the women enter a competition to win a trip to Hawaii; this process puts strain on their relationships.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-06-18</FirstAired>
<Network>Logo</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0497350</IMDB_ID>
<id>244881</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>75435</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Gastineau Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>text/75435.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Meet the Gastineau Girls. No, they're not sisters. They're a mother-daughter duo of New York socialites who are best friends--and sometimes each other's biggest competition. Lisa, the mother, is a former model who made mad money in a divorce settlement with NFL star hubby Mark Gastineau (and invested rather well afterward, thank you very much). Brittny, the daughter, hasn't worked a day in her life. She lived with her grandmother after her parents' divorce and is now moving back to her mother's NYC pad after leaving college in Alabama. They're both looking for fame, fortune, happiness and true love--not really in that order. Good thing there's Luo the doorman-commentator to help guide us through the girls' adventures, because in the first episode alone, the mom and daughter pose for a naked photo shoot, have a surprise birthday party for Lisa and, oh yeah, shop a lot.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2005-02-01</FirstAired>
<Network>E!</Network>
<zap2it_id>SH721379</zap2it_id>
<id>75435</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>262663</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Gokicha!! Cockroach Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/262663-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>A heartwarming story about a cockroach girl who tries to be liked by humans while dodging the insecticide.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-09-14</FirstAired>
<id>262663</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>281667</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls Aloud: Ten Years at the Top</SeriesName>
<Overview>Girls Aloud: Ten Years at the Top is a documentary released to coincide with the tenth anniversary of British all-female pop group Girls Aloud. The documentary follows Girls Aloud from their formation on the ITV reality television programme Popstars: The Rivals to their reunion after a three-year hiatus.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-12-15</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>2607962</IMDB_ID>
<id>281667</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>255929</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Hooters Dream Girls</SeriesName>
<Overview>Hooters girls compete in an opportunity to win Hooters dream girl of the year! </Overview>
<id>255929</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>254378</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Bomb Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/254378-g4.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Set in the 1940s, "Bomb Girls" tells the remarkable stories of the women who risked their lives in a munitions factory building bombs for the Allied forces fighting on the European front. The series delves into the lives of these exceptional women from all walks of life – peers, friends and rivals – who find themselves thrust into new worlds and changed profoundly as they are liberated from their home and social restrictions.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-01-04</FirstAired>
<Network>Global</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1955311</IMDB_ID>
<id>254378</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>253908</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sorority Girls</SeriesName>
<Overview>Reality series in which female students in Leeds compete to become members of an all new American sorority.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-08-11</FirstAired>
<Network>Channel 4</Network>
<id>253908</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>303520</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Transit Girls</SeriesName>
<Overview>The story follows the relationship between the two girls, Sayuri and Yui, as they start to live together under one roof as step-sisters. Despite their initial distaste for each other and the fact that they couldn't be more opposite in looks and personality, they eventually start to develop feelings for each other... How will their romance take shape?</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-11-07</FirstAired>
<Network>Fuji TV</Network>
<id>303520</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>289763</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>THE iDOLM@STER Cinderella Girls</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Idolmaster: Cinderella Girls</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/289763-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>A girl aiming to become an idol named Uzuki Shimamura is informed that she has been accepted into the Cinderella Project, a new project that collects girls and polishes them to become idols. After meeting Rin Shibuya, Mio Honda, and the other eleven fellow members of the group, the girls begin their journey at the 346 Pro talent agency, overcoming many trials and hoping to one day stand on the same stage as their senior idols.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-01-10</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo MX</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt4219136</IMDB_ID>
<id>289763</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>81426</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girl's High</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Girl's High School Students|Girls High|Joshi Kousei</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/81426-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Eriko and her friends Yuma and Ayano are excited about entering high school. Their excitement leads to their breaking of the rules when they toured the school before the opening ceremony. They find out their preconceptions about the all female school may not be as true as they had first thought. Despite that, Eriko and her friends are joined by new friends. They aim to get through high school life together. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2006-04-04</FirstAired>
<id>81426</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>260682</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Thelma's Gypsy Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/260682-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Dressmaker Thelma Madine, from Big Fat Gypsy Weddings, has a reputation for creating incredible wedding dresses for gypsies and travellers, and has worked closely with the community for over 15 years. But now Thelma's decided she wants to give something back to the people who put her on the map.

With business booming, Thelma needs to expand to keep up with demand. So she's taking on a group of inexperienced gypsy and traveller girls as trainees.

But with no prior work experience, can these young girls really learn to make such intricate dresses in just six months?

For the girls, it's the chance of a lifetime, but Thelma has worked hard to gain the trust of the community - one false move and the dream could be over...</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-07-08</FirstAired>
<Network>Channel 4</Network>
<id>260682</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>247151</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls' Generation Goes to School</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/247151-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Girls' Generation Goes to School is a South Korean reality show starring the popular South Korean girl group Girls' Generation.  The show documents the debut of the nine members of Girls' Generation and their associated troubles and ventures. Most of the episodes revolve around the group's unofficial debut and first public performances through the M.net show, School of Rock.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-07-27</FirstAired>
<id>247151</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>165521</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls Gone Wild - Hottest Girl in America</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/165521-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Climb aboard GGW's private jet and million-dollar tour bus as the Girls Gone Wild® camera crews hit America's wildest clubs, campuses, and beaches to meet thousands of wild college girls who will do anything to be voted the Hottest Girl in America.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-05-14</FirstAired>
<Network>HDNet</Network>
<id>165521</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>83749</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Katherine Lynch's Working Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/83749-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Katherine Lynch's Working Girls is a three-part mockumentary series which follows the professional lives of 3 very different Irish women - all of them played by the talented comic performer Katherine Lynch.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-01-16</FirstAired>
<Network>RTÉ</Network>
<id>83749</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>186911</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Samurai Girls</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Hyakka Ryōran Samurai Girls|Hyakka Ryouran: Samurai Bride|Hyakka Ryouran: Samurai Girls</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/186911-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The story takes place in Japan in the early 21st century, in an alternate reality where the Tokugawa Shogunate has remained in power. In this reality, student councils are tasked with oppressing schools. Yagyuu Muneakira is a high school student who rebels against his student council with the help of girls who've had the names of famous samurai heroes passed on to them.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-09-03</FirstAired>
<Network>AT-X</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2074011</IMDB_ID>
<id>186911</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>283932</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Hi-sCool! Seha Girls</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Hi sCoool! Seha Girls</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/283932-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The story of the anime revolves around Dreamcast, Sega Saturn, and Mega Drive, who have just enrolled in SeHaGaga Academy at Tokyo's Haneda Ōtorii station. They are given an assignment needed to graduate by a suspicious teacher, and to clear this assignment, the girls need to enter the world of Sega games. The girls must try their best to graduate without incident.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-10-08</FirstAired>
<Network>Animax</Network>
<id>283932</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>247822</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls' Generation's Horror Movie Factory</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/247822-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Girls' Generation's Horror Movie Factory is a variety show starring Girls' Generation. The members of the group undergo various acting lessons and tests.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-05-03</FirstAired>
<Network>MBC</Network>
<id>247822</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>70837</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Harry's Girls</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>1963-09-01</FirstAired>
<Network>NBC</Network>
<id>70837</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>79945</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls and Boys - Sex and British Pop</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/79945-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>traces British pop music over the past four decades, examining how it has reflected the changing images and social attitudes of men and women. This series draws on exclusive interviews with key figures from Sandie Shaw to Fatboy Slim.
</Overview>
<Network>BBC Two</Network>
<id>79945</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>252343</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Majikoi - Oh! Samurai Girls! </SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Maji de Watashi ni Koi Shinasai!!|Majikoi</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/252343-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Kawakami City is famous for its strong dedication to its samurai ancestors. A healthy fighting spirit is always valued and it's even an important factor for success at school. Yamato, a second year student from Kawakami Highchool is always with his close friends (4 boys and 3 girls). They have all known each other since they were young and have done many things together. While they have many other friends, this group of seven is a close-knit, inseparable group. They even have a secret base where they meet. With the new semester, they welcome two girls into their group and shortly after things begin to change...</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-10-01</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt3416460</IMDB_ID>
<id>252343</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>255469</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Girls' Generation and the Dangerous Boys</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>SNSD and the dangerous boys</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/255469-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Girls' Generation and the Dangerous Boys (Hangul: 소녀시대와 위험한 소년들, sonyeo sidaewa wiheomhan sonyeondeul). Girls' Generation meets up with five trouble making boys. They split into teams and try to make each of the boys become more respectable. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-12-18</FirstAired>
<Network>jTBC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2212303</IMDB_ID>
<id>255469</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>304839</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>DC Super Hero Girls</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>DC Superhero Girls</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/304839-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>At Super Hero High School, well-known DC heroes attend classes and deal with all the awkwardness of growing up (with the added stress of having superpowers).</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-10-01</FirstAired>
<Network>Boomerang</Network>
<id>304839</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>252710</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Dora's Explorer Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/252710-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Dora is the leader of her group of school friends: Naiya, Kate, Emma and Alana. They're the Explorer Girls, and they work together to solve mysteries, help others in their community and have lots of fun along the way. They're a whole group of heroines with varying interests and talents.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-08-08</FirstAired>
<Network>Nickelodeon</Network>
<id>252710</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73466</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Daddy's Girls</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/73466-g.jpg</banner>
<FirstAired>1994-09-01</FirstAired>
<Network>CBS</Network>
<id>73466</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>103291</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Charger Girl Ju-den Chan</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Fight Ippatsu! Jūden-chan!!|Fight Ippatsu! Juuden-chan!!|Fight, One Shot! Charger Girls!!</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/103291-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>From a planet called "Life Core", which exists parallel to the normal human world, females known as "Jūden-chan" (charger girls) are patrolling the human world in search for individuals who feel depressed and unlucky. These people are ranked from A to F, F being normal and A being near suicidal. When the Jūden-chan find targets ranked C or higher, they charge these people up with the help of electricity in order to improve their mental states. Whilst normally unseen by human eyes, one of these Jūden-chan, Plug Cryostat, accidentally meets a young man who is able to see her, because she was targeting his father (his sister in the anime). This series revolves around the various antics between the main characters and the quest for this Jūden-chan to improve herself.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-06-25</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo MX</Network>
<id>103291</id>
</Series>
</Data>
