<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>266967</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Mom</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/266967-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>From hit-maker Chuck Lorre comes his next big comedy‐an irreverent and outrageous take on true family love‐and dysfunction. Newly sober single mom Christy struggles to raise two children in a world full of temptations and pitfalls. Testing her sobriety is her formerly estranged mother, now back in Christy's life and eager to share passive-aggressive insights into her daughter's many mistakes.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2013-09-23</FirstAired>
<Network>CBS</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2660806</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH01739816</zap2it_id>
<id>266967</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>299884</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Mom (2015)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/299884-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Yoon Jung Ae (Cha Hwa Yun) raised her 4 kids by herself. Now, her kid already grown up but none of them really care about her. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-09-05</FirstAired>
<Network>MBC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt5321476</IMDB_ID>
<id>299884</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>133931</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Three Dads One Mom</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>One Mom and Three Dads|Three Dads and a Mother|Abbaje Eommahana|Three Fathers, One Mother</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/133931-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Song Na Young and her husband, Jung Sung Min, desperately want a child but her husband is unable to get her pregnant. Her husband's friends decide to help them. But Na Young suddenly loses her husband in an accident and she gives birth to her daughter but does not know which of her husband's friends fathered her child. The father of Na Young's child can either be Han Soo Hyun, Choi Kwang Hee, or Hwang Kyung Tae. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-04-02</FirstAired>
<Network>KBS TV2</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2659290</IMDB_ID>
<id>133931</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>293193</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Angry Mom</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/293193-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>When Jo Gang-Ja attended high school, she was notorious for fighting. She gave birth to her daughter A-Ran in her late teens and became more responsible. Her daughter A-Ran is now a high school student, but A-Ran is bullied at school. Jo Gang-Ja decides to go back to high school to protect her daughter. Jo Gang-Ja becomes a high school student again. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-03-18</FirstAired>
<Network>MBC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt4535826</IMDB_ID>
<id>293193</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>295015</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Pretty Mom</SeriesName>
<Overview>Even mothers were girls once, and although they’re no longer young, it does not mean they cannot love. This warm family drama tells the story of Lee Soon Jin, a mother who raised her four children without a husband and single-handedly ran a restaurant to support their monetary needs.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-04-05</FirstAired>
<Network>KBS TV2</Network>
<id>295015</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>274560</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Hot Mom</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>2013-09-14</FirstAired>
<Network>C-Span</Network>
<id>274560</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>148561</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Teen Mom</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Teen Mom OG</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/148561-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Teen Mom Stars Catelynn Lowell, Maci Bookout, Amber Portwood Returning for New Season</Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-12-08</FirstAired>
<Network>MTV (US)</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1566154</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP01209503</zap2it_id>
<id>148561</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>76791</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Mom, P.I.</SeriesName>
<Overview>This inventive, offbeat Canadian comedy/drama stars Rosemary Dunsmore as a single mother and waitress who works part-time for a crusty private eye (Stuart Margolin). A feisty mother meets a stubborn detective and together they make the sparks fly. The exciting series will keep everyone glued to the TV set.
Mom PI stars Rosemay Dunsmore as Sally Sullivan, a modern mother and working waitress. Sally teams up with Bernie Fox, a grizzled private detective, played by Stuart Margolin, who is part-Mickey Spillane, part-Duke Ellington. His experience and her mother's intuition get them into and out of arson, fraud, theft, and maybe even murder in the working-class areas of a big city.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1990-10-01</FirstAired>
<Network>CBC (CA)</Network>
<id>76791</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>291141</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>World’s Worst Mom</SeriesName>
<Overview>All parents worry about their children, but some over-protective parents take worrying to the extreme. World’s Worst Mom helps high-strung, fearful parents give their kids the freedom they deserve. Host Lenore Skenazy made national news for allowing her nine-year-old son to travel the New York City subway alone, and now she’s helping to control the fears many parents have about societal dangers.

Brimming with intense emotion and drama, World’s Worst Mom offers advice and takes each family through a series of challenges designed to push their boundaries, give their children more freedom, and teaches parents to loosen-up a little when it comes to their kids.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-01-22</FirstAired>
<Network>Discovery</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2243097</IMDB_ID>
<id>291141</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>276373</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Could We Love?</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Can we love|Mom Needs a Man</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/276373-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>This drama tells the story of three women who are all in their late 30′s. These three women consist of a single mother, a housewife and a single woman. Yoon Jung Wan is a woman who divorces after ten years of marriage and live with her son. Kwon Ji Hyun is a housewife who have a daughter. kim Sun Mi is an elegant single woman.

Meanwhile, Oh Kyung Soo is a movie director who has received several awards and he is known as a bad tempered and self conceited. He then gets involved with Yoon Jung Wan. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-01-06</FirstAired>
<Network>jTBC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt3453936</IMDB_ID>
<id>276373</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>304535</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Married By Mom and Dad</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Married By Mom &amp; Dad</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/304535-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Married By Mom and Dad
new social experiment, men and women who have been unlucky in love have agreed to put their love lives and their future in the hands of the people who know them best: their parents.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-12-13</FirstAired>
<Network>TLC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt5314668</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP02304923</zap2it_id>
<id>304535</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>296279</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Tiger Mom</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Tiger Mom, Kitten Dad</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/296279-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Luo Qian Qian may be spoiled, but that all comes to an end when her mother Bi Sheng discovers academic competition is fierce in elementary school. Determined to make up for lost time, Bi Sheng transforms into a fierce "tiger mom" hell bent on excellence at all costs. In contrast, Qian Qian's father Luo Su believes their daughter's happiness ranks higher than her academic performance. Meanwhile, both sets of grandparents weigh in, while Luo Su's gentle ex resurfaces. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-05-03</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt3740548</IMDB_ID>
<id>296279</id>
</Series>
</Data>
