<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>269550</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Bitten</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/269550-g9.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Based on the New York Times best-selling novels by Canadian author Kelley Armstrong, BITTEN is an emotionally charged thriller that follows reluctant heroine Elena Michaels, the world's only female werewolf, who is forced to take on life-threatening responsibilities, in a male dominated world. The werewolves are monitored by The Pack, a powerful, organized werewolf family based in the grand manor of Stonehaven, the place where Elena's life as a werewolf began. When a dead girl is discovered in the woods outside the town of Bear Valley (the adopted home of The Pack), it’s the genesis of an all-out war against a rogue group of  Mutts (non-Pack werewolves) whose aim is to destroy The Pack. Torn between the new life she’s created in Toronto and loyalty to her Pack family, Elena will fight her own battle between the woman, and the wolf within.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-01-11</FirstAired>
<Network>Space</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2365946</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP01822881</zap2it_id>
<id>269550</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>299598</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>I Was Bitten</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/299598-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The subtitle "... And Somehow Survived" could accompany this series that goes around the world to tell the stories of victims of near-fatal animal bites, stories bolstered with actual photos and video footage. 

From the arid deserts of the Southwestern United States to the lethal waters of Australia, I Was Bitten features victims of the most intense, gruesome, near fatal bites from around the world - with actual photo and video footage. Both the victims and the doctors involved in saving them are interviewed, and the the fascinating science behind the bite is explored, which reveals the devastating aftermath of lethal toxins in the human body.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-08-31</FirstAired>
<Network>Discovery</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1288179</IMDB_ID>
<id>299598</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>279014</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Biter Bitten</SeriesName>
<Overview>This series is about the four close friends and their family looking for a buried treasure from the "Ten Tigers". They go through a lot of clues to lead them to new discoveries which all lead up to the big treasure. Jo Jun-Fung (Benny Chan) is the smart one that loves to solve riddles and answer IQ questions. Cheung Kin-Sing (Michael Tong) is Fung's best friend and both of them just arrived from America after studying.
As the series progresses, their love relationships become entangled causing misunderstandings and difficult times. Sing liked Lo Dan (Linda Chung) at first sight. Joey Chik Ho-Yee (Shirley Yeung) is annoyed with Fung and Sing and they always prank each other, But later she gradually grows a relationship for Fung. But Fung likes Dan and she likes him too, and Sing and Joey try to break them up through hilarious plans which backfire on them instead. They soon start to fall in love with each other. The four strive to get the treasure for historical purposes but little do they know, the deeper they go, the more trouble awaits them.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2006-03-20</FirstAired>
<Network>TVB</Network>
<id>279014</id>
</Series>
</Data>
