<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>249882</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Awkward.</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/249882-g6.jpg</banner>
<Overview>"Awkward" takes an irreverent look at the conflict, chaos and humor that defines teenage life through the eyes of 15-year-old Jenna Hamilton (Ashley Rickards) whose life begins to change when a simple accident becomes an epic misunderstanding and is blown way out of proportion.
Narrated in the first-person voice of Jenna's blog posts, "Awkward." captures the humor within the struggles and experiences everyone can relate to from their formative years. The series picks up in the aftermath of the accident as she must deal with a new not-so-fun stigma, while at the same time managing the other daily drama that comes with being a teenager. From a secret relationship with a popular guy, to being undermined by a mean girl, and parents who just don't get it-Jenna's misfortune will eventually serve as the catalyst for amazing change, but it's not without some missteps and mishaps along the way.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-07-19</FirstAired>
<Network>MTV (US)</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1663676</IMDB_ID>
<id>249882</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>296850</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>So Awkward</SeriesName>
<Overview>A sitcom about three very academically bright, but socially awkward 13 year old girls, trying to make sense of life, boys and fitting in. Straight A, super-nerds LILY, MARTHA and JAS are an inseparable trio, bound together by brains, loyalty and embarrassment.

While other girls their age are going to parties, netball practice and sleepovers, Lily, Martha and Jas are busy with chess club, homework and Friday nights in watching documentaries. They just don’t fit in with their peers and they don’t want to. They obsess over their grades, are baffled by teen trends, and have absolutely no understanding of boys. 

In spite of their ups and downs they are learning that it’s not only ok to be different, it’s important. They have their own unique take on the world and, crucially, they have each other. While they might be the three smartest girls in the class, they’ve got a lot to learn. But that doesn’t stop them from trying…</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-05-21</FirstAired>
<Network>CBBC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt4735850</IMDB_ID>
<id>296850</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>229651</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Awkward Embraces</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/229651-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The series follows the dating adventures and misadventures of three L.A. girls who prove that just because a girl is hot, it doesn't necessarily follow that she has a man, or even that she'd know what to do with one if she got one.  Jessica, the Star Trek/comic book geeky girl, seems to always say and do just the wrong thing at the wrong time to the wrong guy, proving that, well, "Nerdy girls need love, too."</Overview>
<IMDB_ID>tt1833839</IMDB_ID>
<id>229651</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>261113</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Misadventures of Awkward Black Girl</SeriesName>
<Overview>J, an awkward black girl, navigates the embarrassing minefield of love, friendship, and office politics.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-02-03</FirstAired>
<Network>YouTube</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2123765</IMDB_ID>
<id>261113</id>
</Series>
</Data>
