<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>299350</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Casual</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/299350-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>CASUAL is a single-camera, half-hour comedy series that follows the story of a dysfunctional family trying to help each other navigate the modern dating scene. Recent divorcee Tara and her bachelor brother coach each other through the crazy world of dating (on-line and off), while living under the same roof again for the second time and raising her teenage daughter.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-10-07</FirstAired>
<Network>Hulu</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt4577466</IMDB_ID>
<id>299350</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>300393</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Jazz Casual</SeriesName>
<Overview>Jazz Casual was an occasional series on jazz music on National Educational Television (NET), the predecessor to the Public Broadcasting Service (PBS). The show was produced by Richard Moore and KQED of San Francisco, California. Episodes ran for 30 minutes.

It ran from 1961 to 1968 and was hosted by jazz critic Ralph Gleason. The series had a pilot program in 1960. That episode, however, has been destroyed. 31 episodes were broadcast; 28 episodes survive. Most episodes included short interviews with the group leaders.
</Overview>
<FirstAired>1961-10-17</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0290965</IMDB_ID>
<id>300393</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>282757</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Casual Vacancy</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/282757-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Pagford is a seemingly idyllic English village with a cobbled market square and ancient abbey. Behind the pretty façade, however, is a town at war: rich at war with poor, teenagers at war with their parents, wives at war with their husbands, teachers at war with their pupils. A miniseries adaptation of J.K. Rowling's novel.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-02-15</FirstAired>
<Network>BBC One</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2554946</IMDB_ID>
<id>282757</id>
</Series>
</Data>
