<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>123581</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Episodes</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/123581-g5.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Episodes follows the lives of Sean and Beverly Lincoln, British sitcom producers who are persuaded to move to Hollywood and remake their series for an American audience. When the couple is forced to cast Matt LeBlanc in the lead role, a bizarre triangle is formed that strains their marriage and threatens their show.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-01-09</FirstAired>
<Network>Showtime</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1582350</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP01352131</zap2it_id>
<id>123581</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>70502</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Preston Episodes</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/70502-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>A recently divorced English professor, David Preston, leaves his teaching position to pursue his dream of becoming a prize-winning journalist. His new job as an underpaid copy editor at a tabloid magazine called "Stuff" puts his career values to the test. The eccentric staff at "Stuff" includes: Larry Dunhill, the editor who rebels against David's attempts to increase the integrity of the publication; Kelly Freeman, a burned out, one-time award-winning writer who left the world of real news to escape ulcers and anxiety; Harlow, a paranoid, passive-aggressive researcher who gets defensive when things don't go his way; and the smug, corporate-climbing head of personnel, Adam Green, a former student of Preston's whom Preston had once flunked. When David makes this drastic move from academia to the big city, he rents a tiny apartment that comes complete with a quirky, ne'er-do-well neighbor named Derek.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1995-09-01</FirstAired>
<Network>FOX (US)</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0112127</IMDB_ID>
<id>70502</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>179701</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Superfriends: The Lost Episodes</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/179701-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Possible merge needed

http://thetvdb.com/?tab=series&amp;id=72080&amp;lid=7

Airing as part of The Superman/Batman Adventures on USA in 1995, these episodes are known as "The Lost Episodes" because they were animated in 1983 but not aired as ABC dropped the series from their 1983-1984 Saturday morning television line-up.  The mainstay super heroes Batman, Robin, Superman, Wonder Woman, and Aquaman star in these much-loved Super Friends episodes. </Overview>
<FirstAired>1995-01-09</FirstAired>
<Network>USA Network</Network>
<id>179701</id>
</Series>
</Data>
