<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>284210</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Colony</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/284210-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Set in the near future, Los Angeles has been walled-off and isolated by a mysterious occupying force. “Colony” centers on a family torn by opposing forces, struggling to balance difficult decisions to stay together while trying to survive in the new world order.

While some people choose to collaborate with the authorities and benefit from the occupation, others rebel and suffer the consequences. Former FBI agent Will Bowman has a more complicated role: he's being forced to collaborate with the proxy government in order to protect his family and recover his son, who was separated during the initial invasion.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2016-01-14</FirstAired>
<Network>USA Network</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt4209256</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP02250426</zap2it_id>
<id>284210</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>105521</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Colony</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/105521-g4.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The Colony is a controlled experiment to see exactly what it would take to survive and rebuild under these circumstances. For 10 weeks, a group of 10 volunteers, whose backgrounds and expertise represent a cross-section of modern society, are isolated in an urban environment outside Los Angeles and tasked with creating a livable society

With no electricity from the grid, no running water and no communication with the outside world, all the volunteers have to work with are their skills and whatever tools and supplies they can scavenge from their surroundings.

Experts from the fields of homeland security, engineering and psychology have helped design the world of The Colony to reflect elements from both real-life disasters and models of what the future could look like after a global viral outbreak.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-07-21</FirstAired>
<Network>Discovery</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1470018</IMDB_ID>
<id>105521</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>302419</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Roanoke: Search for the Lost Colony</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/302419-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>For over 400 years, the disappearance of 117 colonists from Roanoke Island has been America’s oldest mystery. Now, a mysterious stone inscription may lead to uncovering the truth. Expert stonemasons Jim and Bill Vieira team up with maverick archaeologist Fred Willard to investigate the mystery and find out what happened to the lost colony.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2015-10-26</FirstAired>
<Network>History</Network>
<zap2it_id>EP02266694</zap2it_id>
<id>302419</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>142011</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Colony (Australia)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/142011-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Australia’s first living history series is a blend of historical discovery, social jeopardy, adventure challenge and experiential learning as pampered 21st Century ‘pioneers’ attempt to prove they’re tough enough to survive their historical ordeal. Against this backdrop, the series explores the gripping story of the first settlements.

This six-part series transports a group of English, Irish and Australians, both Indigenous and European, back in time to the Australia of their ancestors. Living the life of free settlers, convicts and local Aboriginal people, they experience the unforgiving toughness of the colony of New South Wales as it was 200 years ago.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2005-01-26</FirstAired>
<Network>SBS</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0825504</IMDB_ID>
<id>142011</id>
</Series>
</Data>
