<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>79168</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Friends</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/79168-g5.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Six young people, on their own and struggling to survive in the real world, find the companionship, comfort and support they get from each other to be the perfect antidote to the pressures of life.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1994-09-22</FirstAired>
<Network>NBC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0108778</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP00115127</zap2it_id>
<id>79168</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>251908</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Haganai</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Boku ha Tomodachi ga Sukunai|Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai |I Don't Have Many Friends|Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai	Next</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/251908-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Hasegawa Kodaka is a recent transfer student to St. Chronica's Academy, a Catholic high school. As with every other school he has ever attended, he finds it difficult to make friends there because of his naturally-blond hair (inherited from his deceased English mother) and fierce-looking eyes, which make him look like a dangerous "yankee" to his prejudiced schoolmates.

One day, Kodaka accidentally comes across the equally solitary and very abrasive Yozora Mikazuki while she converses with her imaginary friend Tomo. Realizing that neither of them have any social lives, they decide that the best way to improve their situation is to form a club – the Neighbor's Club – precisely intended to make friends and learn social skills.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-10-07</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo Broadcasting System</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2645500</IMDB_ID>
<id>251908</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>264933</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Angel's Friends</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/264933-g.jpg</banner>
<FirstAired>2009-10-12</FirstAired>
<Network>Italia 1</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1731708</IMDB_ID>
<id>264933</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73249</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Miss Spider's Sunny Patch Friends</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/22359-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>This exciting animated adventure is set during the first days of spring, when Miss Spider and Holley welcome five new additions to the family Snowdrop, Pansy, Wiggle, Spinner, and Squirt. Trouble arises when the precocious Squirt sets out on his own to return a chicken egg to its owner, forcing Miss Spider and Holley to embark on a dangerous journey to return him to safety. Filled with stellar animation, Miss Spider's Sunny Patch Friends is a release that children will want to revisit again and again. Miss Spider keeps on bringing more and more people into her family such as newcomers, Dragon and Bounce. This series is sure to make you happy and teach you some educational bug facts. Miss Spider's Sunny Patch Friends is a great show that will keep you and your kid attached to. Watch the great new series on Nick Jr. at 10:00AM and on Saturdays on CBS at 12:30N. This new show is sure to keep you interested for a very long time and new episodes are coming frequently so keep a look out for</Overview>
<FirstAired>2004-09-01</FirstAired>
<Network>Nickelodeon</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0428138</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH680360</zap2it_id>
<id>73249</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>72001</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>My Little Pony 'n Friends</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>My Little Pony|My Little Pony and Friends</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/72001-g4.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Ponyland is a mystical land, home to all kinds of magical creatures. The Little Ponies make their home in Paradise Estate, living a peaceful life filled with song and games. However, not all the creatures of Ponyland are so peaceful, and the Ponies often find themselves having to fight for survival against witches, trolls, goblins and all the other beasts that would love to see the Little Ponies destroyed, enslaved or otherwise harmed.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1986-09-01</FirstAired>
<Network>Syndication</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0184761</IMDB_ID>
<id>72001</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>99721</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Friends (2002)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/99721-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Tomoko, a Japanese tourist, and Ji-Hoon, a South Korean film student, meet in Hong Kong. Despite a rocky meeting and their language barrier, they become good friends. In time, they eventually head back to their respective countries but only after exchanging email addresses – promising to keep in touch and eventually meet again. But with fate pushing them to see each other again, Tomoko decides to go to South Korea to meet Ji-hoon again but some problems occur.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2002-02-04</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo Broadcasting System</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0315608</IMDB_ID>
<id>99721</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>82788</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Natsume's Book of Friends</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Natsume Yuujinchou|Natsume Yuujinchou San|Natsume Yuujinchou Shi|Zoku Natsume Yuujinchou</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/82788-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Natsume Takashi has the ability to see spirits, which he has long kept secret. However, once he inherits a strange book that belonged to his deceased grandmother, Reiko, he discovers the reason why spirits surround him. Containing the names of these spirits, a binding contract was formed between the spirits and the owner of the book. Now, Natsume is determined to free the spirits and dissolve the contracts. With the help of a spirit cat, his days are filled trying to return the names to these spirits.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-07-08</FirstAired>
<Network>TV Tokyo</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1414422</IMDB_ID>
<id>82788</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>214421</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Thomas' Trusty Friends</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/214421-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Meet Thomas and his trusty NEW friends at the Sodor Construction Company for lots of action packed new adventurers! Join Jack the Digger, Alfie the Excavator, Kelly the Crane and loads of other great new characters as they work hard and play hard under the watchful eye of Miss Jenny who's always there to make sure her machines do a job "spot on"!</Overview>
<FirstAired>2006-10-01</FirstAired>
<id>214421</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>263556</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Something Special - We're All Friends</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/263556-g.jpg</banner>
<FirstAired>2012-10-22</FirstAired>
<Network>CBeebies</Network>
<id>263556</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>278819</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>One Week Friends</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Isshuukan Friends</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/278819-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Kaori Fujimiya is always alone because all of her happy memories, including time spent with her friends, disappear every Monday. Deciding that he wants to be friends with her anyway, Yuuki Hase tries to get close to Kaori each week, wishing that she would one day call him "a friend."</Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-04-07</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo MX</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt3481364</IMDB_ID>
<id>278819</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>76973</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Friends (1979)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/76973-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Welcome to the Friends (1979) guide at TV Tome. Show Type: Comedy/Drama Three eleven-year-old children--black Randy, product-of-a-broken-home Nancy and leader Pete--grow up in a small California town, dealing with the typical problems of a '70s adolescent. This show was cancelled after 5 episodes. There is no editor for this show. If you would like to be the editor look here for details.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1979-03-01</FirstAired>
<Network>ABC (US)</Network>
<id>76973</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>79323</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Foster's Home for Imaginary Friends</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/28101-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>What happens when children outgrow their imaginary friends? They take them to Madame Foster's Home for Imaginary Friends, a vast Victorian mansion with endless rooms and hundreds of thought-up playmates. At the heart of the story is Blooregard (aka Bloo), an imaginary friend created by an eight-year-old boy named Mac. Although he's usually shy, Mac feels confident when Bloo's around. Bloo, on the other hand, is bold and self-assured, and often gets himself into a mess by acting before he thinks. Follow the adventures of Mac and Bloo in a world where imaginary friends actually come to life. Nothing is ever mundane when you hang out at "Foster's Home for Imaginary Friends"!</Overview>
<FirstAired>2004-08-13</FirstAired>
<Network>Cartoon Network</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0419326</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP00677262</zap2it_id>
<id>79323</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>306111</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Rage of Bahamut: Manaria Friends</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Shingeki no Bahamut: Manaria Friends</AliasNames>
<Overview>Mobile game developer Cygames has opened an official website for a TV anime titled Shingeki no Bahamut: Manaria Friends, scheduled for 2016. It is an adaptation of a popular event, Manaria Mahou Gakuin (Manaria Magic Academy), within the Shingeki no Bahamut social game.
</Overview>
<id>306111</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>304801</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Haburashi / Onna Tomodachi</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Toothbrush / Female Friends</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/304801-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>They were high school classmates, spent their youth together in the school choir and certainly had similar dreams. But one rainy night 20 years later, Furusawa Mizue suddenly shows up at the home of popular scriptwriter Makabe Suzune, with her young son. She has lost her job, money and even the home she lived in. Claiming that Suzune is the only one she can turn to, Mizue beseeches Suzune to let her stay for one night. However, this quickly becomes a promise to stay until she gets employment. Unable to cruelly thrust mother and child away, Suzune’s daily life and work get disrupted. Then, a series of strange incidents start to happen to Suzune’s surroundings. Through this reunion of two classmates who have led completely different lives, all sorts of dormant feelings erupt and memories that they were starting to be forgotten are resurrected.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2016-01-05</FirstAired>
<Network>NHK</Network>
<id>304801</id>
</Series>
</Data>
